

Stewen Ascari

Software developer

My Contact

ssa.steweb@gmail.com

(L) +55 (83) 9 8194-1669

João Pessoa, Brazil

stewenascari.github.io

Skills

- Back-end
 - Java
 - · Spring Boot and all your universe
 - Node.Js
 - Django
 - Python
 - Ruby (studying)
 - Flutter (studying)
- Front-end
 - JavaScript (ES6) | Type script
 - Angular.js
 - React.js (studying)
 - Vue.js
 - ¡Query | CSS3 | HTML5 | Bootstrap
- Database
 - MySQL
 - PostgreSQL
 - SQLServe
 - Mongo (studying)
- Tools
 - Docker
 - AWS
 - Docker compose
 - Github
 - GIT
 - Agile methodology experience

About Me

I specialize in creating efficient software solutions to solve problems and meet customer needs. I have knowledge in several programming languages, such as Java, Python, JavaScript, among others, as well as experience in web development (more than 3 years) and mobile (in learning). In addition, I am very familiar with agile methodologies, which allow me to work collaboratively in a team and deliver projects with speed and great quality.

I have a passion for learning new technologies and I am always aware of industry trends, always looking to update myself to offer the best possible solutions!

Professional Experience

IBM Company | Software Developer

December 2021 - Present

Acting as a full stack dev in the development and maintenance of features in the system, as well as in the creation of new aws services (lambdas, kafkas, sor tables, SQS queue).

Main activities:

- Development of new application features
- Maintenance of existing application features
- Development of new aws services
- Systems integration: Connects different parts of the application, such as front-end and back-end, ensuring that they work together harmoniously.
- clean code culture

Itix Tecnologia - Technological Solutions | Junior full stack developer

February 2021 - December 2021

Actively contributes to the development team to create and improve system features. The technologies that were used: maven, java 8, hibernate, azure, docker, docker-compose, Spring Cloud feign, Spring, PostgreSQL, AngularJS, and TypeScrip.

Main activities:

- Development of new application features
- Maintenance of existing application features
- Systems integration: Connects different parts of the application, such as front-end and back-end, ensuring that they work together harmoniously.
- clean code culture

Soft Skill

- Clean code
- Excellent Communicator Problem Solver Analytical
- Focused
- Friendly
- Eager to learn
- Detail-oriented and able to handle multiple tasks simultaneously

Education

- University of Paraiba
 Bachelor's Degree in Information systems
 Completed in 2018
- CertiProf Professional Knowledge Certificate in Scrum Foundation Professional
- Udemy
 Automated Testing Course
- Project Ayty of Federal University of Paraiba Android Course

Languages

- Portugues native
- English Unrolled

Indra Brazil | Junior full stack developer May 2020 - February 2021

I actively contribute to the development team to create the new system, soon after the system was finalized I was allocated to another project, which in turn was responsible for implementing and maintaining the features in the system. The technologies that were used: maven, java 8, hibernate, Spring boot, Oracle database, AngularJS, and TypeScrip.

Main activities:

- Development of new application features
- · Maintenance of existing application features
- Systems integration: Connects different parts of the application, such as front-end and back-end, ensuring that they work together harmoniously.
- · clean code culture

Koy - Legal Intelligence | Junior full stack developer September 2019 - May 2020

He actively contributes to the development team in the creation and maintenance of automation in the system, as well as in the functionalities. The technologies that were used: selenium, python, gradle, java, hibernate, and PostgreSQL.

Main activities:

- Development of new application features
- Development of new automation using escaping
- Maintenance of existing application features
- Systems integration: Connects different parts of the application, such as front-end and back-end, ensuring that they work together harmoniously.
- · clean code culture

PBPrev | Internship full stack developer January 2019 - August 2019

Actively contributes to the development team to create features for the new system. The technologies that were used: maven, java 8, hibernate, Spring boot, Oracle database, AngularJS, and TypeScrip.

Main activities:

- Development of new application features
- Systems integration: Connects different parts of the application, such as front-end and back-end, ensuring that they work together harmoniously.
- clean code culture